Guide to the Kate Bornstein papers 1910-2018
Brown University Library
- Wrintings by other authors (unpublished), 1986-2014
  - Soloway, Jill: Transparent, Episodes 201 and 202 (television scripts); episode 202 by Micah Fitzerman-Blue, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Stevens, Kelly: Mother's Day (poem), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Straus, Lindsey Marie: Towards a New View of Gender (Unitarian sermon), 2005 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Strickland, Bonnie Ruth: Beauy and the Butch (essay) and Leaving the Confederate Closet (paper), 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Sycamore, Matt Bernstein: Tricks and Treats: Sex Workers Write About Their Clients (manuscript) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Thornton, John: The Dream of Doctor Bantam (manuscript), n.d. (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Trauger, Kody: The Development of Gender and Sexual Identity (proposal) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Tucker, Duncan: Transamerica (film script), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Vanderburgh, Reid: Transitions and Beyod: Observations on Gender Identity (manuscript) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Various authors: "solo" (poems), ca.2004 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Watkins, Christian: Cootie Shots (play description and list of writers), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Wettig, Patricia: F to M (script), 2010 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, Riki Anne: various titles (poems), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Winfield, Cynthia: Gender Identity: The Ultimate Teen Guide (unedited manuscript); includes correspondence, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Subject Files, 1988-2011
  - ACT Theatre Company, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - LGBT centers, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Sadomasochism; includes press and related material re: Permission (play), 1992-2004 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - "Spirtuality/health", 1992-2005 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Suicide, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Transgenderism, 1988-2011 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Print Material, 1980-2017
  - Article: Technoflesh or "Didn't That Hurt?" by Karmen MacKendrick (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Book: Against Equality: Quuer Critiques of Gay Marriage, edited by Ryan Conrad; includes essay by Bornstein and thank you letter from Conrad, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Book: Butch: Not Like Other Girls by SD Holman; contains photo book and signed note to Bornstein from author, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Book: A Rule Is To Break: A Child's Guide to Anarchy by John and Jana; contains signed copy by authors, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Book: Transfigure by Leon Mostovoy, Leon (art photography book), 2014 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Calendar: FMLA; contains feminit calendar with dedication to Bornstein, 2008-2009 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Catalog: Cold Water by Justin Bond; contains art exhibit catalog (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Coloring book: Gender Now: A Learning Adventure for Children and Adults, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Coloring book: Girls Are Not Chicks by Jacita Bunnell and Julia Novak; contains signed copy by the authors (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Coloring book: Girsl Will Be Boys Will Be Girls… by Jacita Bunnell and Irit Reinheimer, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Coloring book: A Sister's Uncut ColoringBook; includes letter to KB from Ali Brumfit and coloring book page depicting Bornstein (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Comic book: Joker's Asylum II: Harley Quinn, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Comic book: Buffy the Vampire Slayer; contains "Tales of the Vampires" and "Last Gleamings," parts one and three, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Journal: Butt, Number 16, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Journal: Cross-talk: The Transgender Community News and Information Monthly, Number 65, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Journal: Girls Like Us Lesbian Quarterly, Number 7, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Journal: Invert: The Journal of Gay and Lesbian Sensibility, Volume 2, Number 4, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Journal: OP: Trans Male Quarterly, Numbers 2-4, 6, 2010-2011 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Journal: Outrageous Women: A Journal of Woman-to-woman S/M, Volume 3, Number 1, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Magazine: All Things News re: student Christian movements in Canada and gay rights in Christianity, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Magazine: The Crisis: Black Women and the Future of Politics, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Magazine: The New York Times Magazine; contains the "Men of Wellesley" Issue, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Magazine: The Rag, Issues 1-2, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Magazine: Reluctant Hero re: teen girlhood, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Magazine: Skeptic re: Scientology, Volume 17, Number 1, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Magazine: Spread: Illuminating the Sex Industry, Volume 2, Issue 3, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Newsletter: P.O.N.Y. [Prostitutes of New York] Press, Volume 1, Number 1, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Poetry book: The Abigail Sonnets by Roz Raveney [signed copy], 2010 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Poetry book: After the Poison by Colin Keeley; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Poetry book: Choke by Stacey Waite; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Poetry book: Dialectic of the Flesh by Roz Kaveney, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Poetry book: Dogs in Lingerie by Danielle Willis, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Poetry book: Domestic Transmission b Madelyn Hatter, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Poetry book: Love Poem to Androgyny by Stacey Waite, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Poetry book: Quarter Life Crisis by "Ela", 2007 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Poetry book: Roaming the Medicine Line by Amanda Austin, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Poetry book: Slow To Burn by Collin Kelley; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Poetry book: Tributaries: Poems Exploring Black History by Andrea Jenkins; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Report: Access to Health Care for Transgender Persons in Greaer Boston, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Report: Bending the Mold: An Acton Kit for Transgender Youth, ca.2004 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Report: Building Trans Justice from the Ground to the Sky, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Report: The Network La Red Annual Report, 2017 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Report: True Colors: Sexual Minority Youth and Family Services of Connecticut Resource Guide (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Zine: Anna: A Souvenir Pitchbook by Kathleen Crawford re: Anna Haining Swan, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Zine: Adventures in Menstruating, Issue 2-6, 2006-2011 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Zine: Art for Art Sake, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Zine: Avoid. Strange. Men, Volume 1, Issue 2, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Zine: Benthology, edited by Toby Langford and Amy Davies, 2005, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Zine: Betwixt: Eleven Poems by Rafe Posey, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Zine: Bitch King: Zine for the Vulva-lution by Angela Chaos, Issue 2; incudes letter to Bornstein from author, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Zine: Burning on Purpose by Maya Hersh, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Zine: Changling Zine by LYRIC's Changlings [trans youth group], n.d. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Zine: Chloroformative Years, Number 16, by Daphne Gottlieb, 2008-2009 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Zine: Cliterature: 18 Interviews with *Women Writers, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Zine: The Comic Book Fan's Worst Nightmare, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Zine: Contribution to a Human Revolution by Jodi Knowles, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Zine: Dance Card by Frankie Bolt, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Zine: Deep Shit by Suzannne Scommodau, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Zine: Different Times: Drag, Life, Rock N' Roll (Five Years in Six Inch Killaz, 1994-1999), 2013 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Zine: Dis Course by Tara Hardy, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Zine: A D.I.Y. Guide to Suicide Prevention by Elijah Corbin; includes inscribed letter to Bornstein, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Zine: Doris 15: D.I.Y. Antidepression Guide, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Zine: Drag by Catherine and Francis; includes letter to Bornstein from author, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Zine: Dysphoria: A Map of Wounds (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Zine: Either/Or by Julia Serano, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Zine: The Eyes of the Man by Suzy Subways [signed copy], n.d. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Zine: The Fishtank: Dykes, Pervs, Queers, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Zine: Friends Make the Best Medicine by the Icarus Project, ca.2006 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Zine: From Here to There and Back Again, Number 1-3, by Shannon, 2005-2007 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Zine: Full-body Halo by Daphne Gottlieb, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Zine: The F-Word: A Feminist Handbook for the Revolution, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Zine: The F-Word: A Feminist Handbook for the Revolution, 2007-2008 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Zine: The Gender Booklet by Boston Bastian, Mel Reiff Hill, and Jay Mays (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Zine: The Gender Community: We Are We Going In the Nineties by Wendy Parker, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Zine: Gender Fuck Me by Jess Dugan, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Zine: Genderflex: A Polygenderous Publication, Volume IV, Issue 21-22, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Zine: High on Burning Photographs, Number 8, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Zine: Hoax, Issue 1-3; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, 2009-2010 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Zine: House of Dames, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Zine: I'll Eat You With My Teeth by Solidad Decosta, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Zine: Intermission: The Body Project As It Begins to Consume My Existance by Mollie, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Zine: It's Not the End of the World! Building A Life With Limp Wrists by Ocean (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Zine: It's Not You. I Just Need Space by Chella Quint, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Zine: Journal of a Transsexual by Diane Leslie Feinberg, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Zine: Kate Bornstein, presented by SU Allies, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Zine: Kind of Animal by Elaine M. Ellis, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Zine: Kind to Call by Brit A. Ashley; includes inscription to Bornstein from author (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Zine: Know Your Rights: A Guide for Public School Stuents in North Carolina, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Zine: Latch by Bess Fernandez, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Zine: Life Doesn't Come With Training Wheels, Volume 1, Issue 1, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Zine: Like Cinderella (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Zine: The Long Walk Back to Myself by Jessica Stein, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Zine: Love You to a Fault by Gio Marcus; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Zine: Luscious Thoughts, Number 2-4, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Zine: M Is For Monster: A One-shot Memoir of Rape and Recovery by Jess (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Zine: Making It: A Woman's Guide to Sex in the Age of AIDS by Cindy Patton and Janis Kelly, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Zine: Manifesto: Selected Poems and Rhymes by Solidad DeCosta (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Zine: Milk-wet Memoirs, Volume 3, by Sandi Strehlau; includes inscription to Bonrstein, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Zine: Misled by the Misled Youth Network, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Zine: Ms, Direction, Number 10, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Zine: Murder Can Be Fun, Number 9/10, 12, 17, and unidentified, 1997, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Zine: Mutant Superpowers and Lithium Pills: Bipolar Adventure Stories by Sascha Scatter, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Zine: My Life As I Remember It by Bobby Miller; includes inscription to Bornstein, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Zine: Naughty Nursie, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Zine: Never Throw Anything in the Fishpond by Ryka Aoki de la Cruz, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Zine: A New Language of Gender and Desire by Tobi Hill-Meyer; includes inscription to Bornstein (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Zine: Non Monogamy: Doin It and Doin It and Doin It Well? (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Zine: Occupation: A Do-it-yourself Guide, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Zine: On Edge, Issue 2-4, 2006-2007 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Zine: Out: 2 North American Jewish Women On the Israeli Occupation of the Palestinian Territories by Iana and Aviva, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Zine: Out of Darkness by Jennifer Prichard, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Zine: Petroleause by Rachel Szego, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Zine: Phurba by Amanda Austin; includes inscription to Bonstein from author, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Zine: Post Modern Queer, Issue Number 1, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Zine: Poundcake by Elaine M. Ellis; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Zine: The Pretty and the Putrid, the Loving and the Loathing by Toby Langford, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Zine: Prostitution Laws, Social Contructs, and Sex Workers Rights, ca.2008 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Zine: The Q File by Generation Q, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Zine: Quarter Inch Squares, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Zine: Queeruption, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Zine: Radical Queer Femnifesto! By Teri Ciacchi; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Zine: Reassess Your Weapons, Issue 6, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Zine: Rebel Fux!, Issue 1, 3-4, 9-11, 14, 25, and special issue, edited by Kate Huh [fragile], 1996-2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Zine: The Red Anger by Marge Houdini, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Zine: Revolutions Per Minute by Colleen Matthews and Tara Orlowski, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Zine: Saint Card I Found in Her Purse by Tamara Llosa-Sander, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Zine: Scent: The Zine by Shoshana Rosenfeld and Mollie Biewald (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Zine: Shoulder Strap Slip by Tara Hardy; includes inscribed letter to Bornstein from author, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Zine: S.O.C. E. (Save Our Cultural Exhibits) by Julian Gregory, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Zine: Synthetic Half Breed by Patch Avery; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Zine: Tattoo Trinity by Angela Jones; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Zine: Teen Talk Peer Support Presents Zines re: body Image, mental health, and sexually transmitted infections, 2005, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Zine: Toward the Deconstruction of Schooling by Jan D. Matthews, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Zine: Toward the Queer Insurrection by the Mary Nardini Gang, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Zine: Transfeminism: A Collection by Emi Koyama, 1999-2001 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Zine: Trans-inspired Writings by Chris Lu; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Zine: Transzine!, Issue 2 and 4, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Zine: Transzilla!, Issue 1-2, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Zine: Two Essays by Emma Goldman on Youth Liberation, reprinted by the Florida Radical Student Union, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Zine: Up, Issue 5-6, 10-11, 13, and unnumbered, by Mollie, 1998-2000, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Zine: Unforgivens by Tara Hardy, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Zine: Untitled, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Zine: The Urban Spook Show, Issue 10, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Zine: Various titles by Jasmine Hoover; includes "The Special People's Club," "Zine for Your Dollie," and letter to Bornstein from author [fragile], ca.2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Zine: View From the Road: A Limited Edition Photo Essay by Kate Bornstein, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Zine: Virginia by Kate Bornstein re: Virginia Ramey Mollenkott, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Zine: What the Brain Forgets, and the Heart Denies, the Body Remembers by Heather M. 'Acs (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Zine: What Happens When the Screen Breaks by Ryka Aoki De La Cruz; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Zine: Wired Zine by Myra Long and the Ohio State University Women's Center (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Zine: Xambunctious by Max Cohen, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Zine: Yank by Tara Hardy, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Zine: Your World Can't Fucking Kill Me! By Click; includes inscription to Bornstein from author, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Ephemera, 1991-2005
  - Bandada, patch, and medal from the QueerScouts (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Buttons, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Calendar re: Pug dogs by Barbara and Frances Carrellas [canine] and Bornstein, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Drawings and illustrations (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Flyers and information sheets (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Graphic imagery, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Graphic imagery: "Tatto - Summer 2005" (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Other ephemera, 1991, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Postcards, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Postcards, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Programs for events, 1999-2003 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Stickers, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Photographs, 1910-2017
  - Alan Bornstein (1 of 2), ca.1963-1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Alan Bornstein (2 of 2), ca.1965 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Albert Bornstein (1 of 3), 1948-1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Albert Bornstein (2 of 3), ca.1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Albert Bornstein (3 of 3), 1969-1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Albert Bornstein bar mitzvah, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Albert Bornstein on stage (1 of 2), ca.1966-1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Albert Bornstein on stage (2 of 2), ca.1966-1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Albert Bornstein weddings, ca.1975-1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Albert Bornstein with Alan Bornstein [brother], ca.1948-1963 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Albert Bornstein with family and relatives, ca.1958-1963 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Albert Bornstein with girlfriends, ca.1963 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Albert Bornstein with girlfriends, ca.1968-1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Albert Bornstein with Jessica Leah Bornstein [daughter], 1973 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Albert Bornstein with Jessica Leah Bornstein [daughter], ca.1983 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - "Audience polaroids from 1994 run of Virtually Yours taken by Diane C. [?]" (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Barbara Carrellas headshot; contains photograph by Annie Sprinkle, ca.2000 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - College images at Brown University, 1966-1969 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Family, ca.1910-1939 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Family, ca.1940-1969 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Family, ca.1969-2002 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Family slides, ca.1948-1951 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Gender conference panel; includes photographs of Judith Butler (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Grandfather [fragile image] (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - International Foundation for Gender Education conference (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Kate Bornstein; includes image of Bornstein at year of sex reassignment surgery (1 of 5), 1986-2017 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Kate Bornstein (2 of 5), 1986-2017 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Kate Bornstein; contains black and white contact sheets (3 of 5), 1986-2017 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Kate Bornstein (4 of 5 ), 1986-2017 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Kate Bornstein (5 of 5), 1986-2017 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Kate Bornstein on stage (1 of 2), 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Kate Bornstein on stage (2 of 2), 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Kate Bornstein speaking at censorship protest, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Kate Bornstein undergoing cancer treatment (1 of 2), ca.1996 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Kate Bornstein undergoing cancer treatment (2 of 2), ca.1996 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Kate Bornstein with Barbara Carrellas (1 of 2), ca.1995-2005 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Kate Bornstein with Barbara Carrellas (2 of 2), ca.1995-2006 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Kate Bornstein with Caitlin Sullivan (1 of 2), ca.1990-1995 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Kate Bornstein with Caitlin Sullivan (2 of 2), ca.1990-1996 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Kate Bornstein with others (1 of 3), ca.1989-2015 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Kate Bornstein with others (2 of 3), ca.1989-2016 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Kate Bornstein with others (3 of 3), ca.1989-2017 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Locations, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Mildred Vandam Bornstein [mother]; includes images of Albert/Kate Bornstein with mother (1 of 2), ca.1930-1994 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Mildred Vandam Bornstein [mother]; includes images of Albert/Kate Bornstein with mother (2 of 2), ca.1930-1995 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Other people (1 of 3), ca.1990-1999 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Other people (2 of 3), ca.1990-2000 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Other people (3 of 3), ca.1990-2001 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Paul Bornstein [father] (1 of 2), ca.1924-1969 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Paul Bornstein [father] (2 of 2), ca.1924-1970 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Paul and Mildred Bornstein [parents] (1 of 2), ca.1950-1974 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Paul and Mildred Bornstein [parents] (2 of 2), ca.1950-1975 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Pets [family], ca.1940-1949 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Pets, ca.1995 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Pride parades (1 of 2), ca.1990 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Pride parades (1 of 2), ca.1990 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Queers Up North conference [contact sheet], n.d. (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Unidentified romantic partner, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Unidentified romantic partner, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Oversize material
  - Oversize Box 17X: Correspondence from "Time Out Youth" members, family photograph scrapbook (unbound), Posters for lectures and performances by Bornstein, and Transfigurations photography book by Jana Marcus, 1940-2006 (Box 17X)
  - Oversize Box 18XXX: Get-well posters inscribed by friends and family during Bornstein's cancer treatment, and extra large posters for lectures and performances by Bornstein (Box 18XXX)
- Electronic records on removable carriers
  - 3.5 inch disk: "Loren Cameron, press kit image and flyer, body alchemy" (Box 19)
  - 6.35mm film: "Hidden: A Gender master" (Box 19)
  - 16mm Anscochrome film: "April '58, Mildred and Essie, P.K.B. and family", 1958 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (large box): "10 yr old Albert in bondage [recto]; Paul, Albert Mildred - Williamsburg '58 [verso]", 1958 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (large box): "Albert's circus 9/58", 1958 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (large box): "Albert [?] - June 1959" (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (large box): "Geo. School, Pittsburgh, Fall '57", 1957 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (large box): "Grad. After party - 6/58, Big Al's fold, Clane family (8/58)", 1958 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (large box): "Pennington - '64", 1964 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "1959 - January, Rocky -, boys from Moravian [?] playing basketball" (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "1962 Pennington family" (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "1969, Brown U. Al graduation" (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "A.H.B. - boardwalk 3/55, Pompton - M.B. - A.H.B., AVB 3/55", 1955 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "Al, Judy, Rocky and Albert and Paul, Summer '59", 1959 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "Albert's graduation, Pennington '65 I", 1965 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "Albert's graduation, Pennington '65 II" (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "Alan and Albert first few minutes, then fishing [recto]; Al and Ab Monday morn fish 12/55 [verso]", 1955 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "Alan and Albert space helmes, Pompton Lakes, KY derby", 1952-1953 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "FLA '54", 1954 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "FLA '54 [?, I [illegible]", 1954 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "FLA '54 Geo. School and Spring Valley Motel", 1954 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "Florida, Albert, Pompton 1951 (March)" (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "La Riviera X-mas '55", 1955 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "Mt Vernon - 9/55", 1955 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "Pennington, June '64, Maud Conavaggion [?], John - Albert, commencement (flag) carrying", 1964 (Box 19)
  - 16mm Kodachrome film (small box): "Pompton Lakes '52", 1952 (Box 19)